http://tidewater.vaems.org/2-general-information/general-information/1605-privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.
What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies? We do not use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Online Privacy Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
Tidewater EMS Council 1104 Madison Plaza Suite 101 Chesapeake, Virginia 23320 Email: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. Telephone: 757-963-0632
Upcoming Events
OMD Update - Virtual
Fri Dec 11 @ 9:00AM - 12:00PM
Education and Training Committee Meeting
Wed Dec 16 @ 9:30AM - 11:30AM
TEMS Quarterly Drug/IV Box Inventory
Wed Dec 16 @ 4:30PM - 04:31PM
Christmas - Office Closed
View Full Calendar
Search ...
TEMS TIME Podcasts
Platinum Partner
Gold Partner
Gold Partner
Gold Partner
Silver Partner
HomeContact the Tidewater EMS StaffAbout Tidewater EMS
About TEMS VideoVision/Mission/Plan/BoardTidewater EMS CouncilHampton Roads MMRSEastern Virginia Healthcare CoalitionCouncil or OEMSOrg DocumentsTEMS History990 FormsConference rooms available
Tidewater EMS Committees & Reports
Annual / Quarterly ReportsMinutes of Committees and Board
Board of DirectorsExecutive CommitteeGovernance CommitteeAudit and Finance CommitteeOperational Medical Directors Committee (OMD)EMS Medical Operations CommitteeEducation CommitteePatient and Provider Safety PI CommitteeStroke Triage PI CommitteeTrauma Triage PI Committee
Description of Committees and Board
Executive CommitteeGovernance CommitteeAudit and Finance CommitteeOperational Medical Directors CommitteeEMS Medical Operations CommitteeEastern Shore EMS CouncilBoard of DirectorsMetropolitan Medical Strike Team
Tidewater EMS Partners
TEMS Partner in Service AwardBecome a Partner of TEMSOur Partners
Tidewater EMS Awards Information
Past EMS Award Recipients
Past State EMS Award WinnersPast Tidewater EMS Award Winners
Tidewater EMS Regional Awards - Start HereTidewater EMS Council Recognized Excellence in EMS 2020
Tidewater EMS Meeting / Event CalendarTidewater EMS Training CalendarState / Regional Education / Training
Training CalendarOMD Online Training CourseEMS Training Programs
State / Regional Testing
State EMT Test Sites
State EMT Test Site (CTS) - TEMS RegionInformationState EMT Test Site (CTS) - Across The State
TEMS Regional ALS Sanctioning Process
TEMS ALS Sanction Boards Policy – Pandemic PolicyTEMS Regional ALS Sanctioning WrittenInformation
Obtaining Legal Recognition/Reciprocity
Tidewater EMS Regional ProtocolsTidewater EMS Drug / IV Box Info
TEMS Drug/IV Box Incident On-line FormPrehospital Drug & IV Box Incident Report InstructionsState Drug Diversion Form (Online Form)TEMS Quarterly Med Box Inventory
TEMS Quarterly Med Box Inventory (Online Form)
TEMS Medication ShortagesTEMS EMS Medication Box Exchange (Short) FormTEMS Drug/IV Box System Information
Tidewater EMS CLIA WaiverInfection Prevention Resources
DICO Information
The Flu and Norovirus Among us
Hand Hygiene Resources
Hand Hygiene Posters & More...Hand Hygiene TrainingHand HygieneShow Me the Science
Infection Prevention Practices / Standard Precautions
CDC: Protecting Healthcare PersonnelEMS Infectious Disease PlaybookHealthcare Infection Control GuidelinesPPE: Personal Protective EquipmentCDC: Diseases and Organisms in Healthcare SettingsStandard Precautions & Transmission-Based Precautions
Infectious Diseases
Clostridium difficle InfectionsEbola
Air Medical Transport Guidance for Ebola PatientsChecklist for Evaluating Patients for EVD in the USEbola Information for EMS Providers, Agencies and SystemsEbola Information for Healthcare WorkersEMS Checklist for Ebola PreparednessEMS Ebola Screening Criteria TemplateEvaluation Algorithm for the Returned TravelerInterim Guidance Patient Management Guidance for EMS & PSAPsMedical Waste ManagementOEMS Ebola Info for Healthcare Workers & EMSPBS "Ebola Outbreak" DocumentariesCDC Ebola PagePets & EbolaPHMSA: Ebola Infectious Waste GuidancePPE: Personal Protective EquipmentPostmortum Care of Human Remains with Ebola
CDC Health Alert Network (HAN)Enterovirus D68
CDC Enterovirus D68 PageAbout Non-Polio Enterovirus InfectionsEnterovirus D68 Prevention Poster Image
Influenza
Infuenza Vaccination for Health Care WorkersSeasonal InfuenzaWeekly U.S. Flu Activity MapACIP: Prevention & Control of Seasonal Influenza
Norovirus
CDC: Norovirus in Healthcare SettingsWhat Healthcare Providers Should KnowFact Sheet: NorovirusNorovirus Infection Control Recommendations
Protect Your Health
What vaccines do you need?
Tuberculosis
TB: Infection Control GuidelinesTB Skin Test Fact SheetTesting for TuberculosisCDC: Tuberculosis PageTuberculin Skin Testing (TST)
Vector Borne Diseases
Zika Virus Disease
About Zika Virus DiseaseCDC's Zika Resources
Disaster Preparedness
General Preparedness Resources
2012 Hurricane Evacuation GuideStorm Surge Maps
Citizen Preparedness
Ready Kids!Ready Hampton RoadsReady Virginia
EMS Agency Preparedness
Continuity Plan TemplateAgency/Business Survival ToolkitBusiness Insurance BasicsContinuity Planning BasicsTest Your Insurance IQ
Insurance & Disasters
Know Your Hurricane DeductibleNatl Flood Insurance ProgramCheck Your InsuranceBusiness Insurance Basics
Military Family Preparedness
Air Force - AFPASSArmy Families - ADPAASCoast Guard ReadyMilitary Family PreparednessNavy - NFAAS
Pet & Animal Preparedness
Animals in Emergencies Video (MPEG)Saving the Whole FamilyReady Pet BrochurePet Friendly LodgingEmergency Contact CardsDisaster Tips: BirdsDisaster Tips: Farm AnimalsDisaster Tips: HorsesPet & Animal PreparednessDisaster Tips: Reptile & Amphibs
Responder Preparedness
Ready Responder PosterConsiderations for 1st RespondersReady Responder Toolkit
Access & Functional Needs Considerations
Planning for Access & Functional NeedsHampton Roads Special Needs Resources
Mass Casualty Preparedness
Mass Casualty Drills & ExercisesMass Casualty Incident Management CoursesVirginia Triage TagsRequest the Hampton Roads MCI Response Guide
RSAF Grant InfoOnline Forms
State Drug Diversion Form (Online Form)TEMS Quarterly Med Box Inventory Online FormTEMS Online PI FormTEMS Drug/IV Box Incident On-line FormRESPONSE / Web Site Content Contributor!EMS Medication Box Exchange (Short) FormER Exchange Form (Page 4 of Appendix F)CISM Post-Intervention Feedback
Tidewater EMS Performance Improvement
PI Info and ResourcesTEMS Online PI FormPI Articles
CISM
Virginia CISM InformationTeam ApplicationTeam Members OnlyTEMS Team Information and ServicesCISM Post-Intervention Feedback
Career and Vol Jobs
Career Information FlyerVolunteer FlyerVirginia EMS Jobs
Tidewater EMS RESPONSE Newsletter
Archived Printed Response - PDF (2003-2016)Submit ContentRESPONSE Newsletters (2017-present)
Hospital Status Info
Hospital Status ListServ Email Sign-Up
Streaming audio from local 911 Centers
Get monthly news, events and more delivered by email. Join the free TEMS electronic list.
nationalcprassociation
Tweets by @TidewaterEMS
www.nationalcprassociation.com
